edgepark.com 2014-03-30

# Privacy Policy - Edgepark Medical Supplies

Edgepark Medical Supplies® Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy applies to our Web sites. 

This Policy describes how we treat personal information we gather on the digital platforms where this policy is located. This includes Web sites and interactive e-mail messages. This policy does not apply to our treatment of information we gather elsewhere. 

This policy also does not apply to how we use and disclose medical and health-related information. For an explanation of how we treat medical and health-related information, [please go here](https://www.edgepark.com/information/documents/NPPVersion1010.pdf).

We collect information from and about you.

**Contact information**. For example, we might collect your name and street address if you request a catalog. We might also collect your phone number or e-mail address.

**Information you submit or post**. ** ** We collect the information you post in a public space on our platforms. This might include our social media pages on third party Web sites. We also collect information when you contact us. Remember, health or medical information we collect is described and governed by our [Notice of Privacy Practices](https://www.edgepark.com/information/documents/NPPVersion1010.pdf).

**Other information**. If you use our Web site, we may collect information about the browser you're using. We might look at what site you came from, or what site you visit when you leave us.

We collect information in different ways. 

**We collect information directly from you**. For example, if you request a catalog. We also collect information if you contact us through the Web site. 

**We collect information from you passively.** We use tracking tools like browser and flash cookies.

**We get information about you from third parties.** For example, our business partners may give us information about you.

We use information as disclosed and described here. 

**We use information to respond to your requests or questions**. For example, we might use your information to send you a catalog. 

**We use information to improve**. We may use your information to make our Web site and products better.  We might use your information to customize your experience with us. We may combine information we get from you with information about you we get from third parties. 

**We use information for security purposes**. We may use information to protect our company, our customers, and our Web site.

**We use information for marketing purposes where permitted by law**. For example, we might send you information about new products and special offers. We might tell you about new features or updates. If you register with us, we might enroll you in our e-mail newsletter. For information about how your medical or health-related information is used with respect to these activities, please read our [Notice of Privacy Practices](https://www.edgepark.com/information/documents/NPPVersion1010.pdf).

**We use information to communicate with you about our relationship**. For example, we might contact you about this Policy or our Web site Terms.

**We use information as otherwise permitted by law.**

We may share information with third parties. 

**We will share information within our company**. This includes to our affiliates and related entities.

**We will share information with third parties who perform services on our behalf**. For example, we share information with vendors who send e-mails and catalogs for us. We may also share information with companies that operate our Web site.  We share medical and health information consistent with our legal obligations and as described in our [Notice of Privacy Practices](https://www.edgepark.com/information/documents/NPPVersion1010.pdf).

**We will share information if we think we have to in order to comply with the law or to protect ourselves.** For example, we will share information to respond to a court order or subpoena. We may share it if a government agency or investigatory body requests. We might share information when we are investigating potential fraud. This might include fraud we think has happened during a sweepstakes or promotion.

**We may share information with any successor to all or part of our business.** For example, if part of our business was sold we may give our customer list as part of that transaction.

**We may share information for other reasons we may describe to you.**

You have certain choices about sharing and marketing practices. 

**You can opt out of receiving our marketing e-mails**. If you are a registered user, please log into your account or see the instructions in our [Notice of Privacy Practices](https://www.edgepark.com/information/documents/NPPVersion1010.pdf). You can also follow the instructions in any promotional message you get from us. Don't worry! Even if you opt out of getting marketing messages, we will still send you transactional messages. These include responses to your questions or information about your purchases.

**You can control cookies and tracking tools.** Your browser may give you the ability to control cookies. How you do so depends on the type of cookie. Certain browsers can be set to reject browser cookies. To control flash cookies you can go [here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html). Why? Because flash cookies cannot be controlled through your browser settings. If you block cookies on your browser, certain features on our sites may not work.

These sites and children. 

Our platforms are meant for adults. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 without permission from a parent or guardian. If you are a parent or legal guardian and think your child under 13 has given us information, you can e-mail us at [edgeparkcareteam@edgepark.com](mailto:edgeparkcareteam@edgepark.com). You can also write to us at the address listed at the end of this policy. Please mark your inquiries "COPPA Information Request."

Parents, you can learn more about how to protect children's privacy on-line [here](http://www.ftc.gov/privacy/privacyinitiatives/childrens_educ.html).

We use standard security measures. 

The Internet is not 100% secure. We cannot promise that your use of our sites will be completely safe. We encourage you to use caution when using the Internet. This includes not sharing your passwords. 

We keep personal information as long as it is necessary or relevant for the practices described in this Policy. We also keep information as otherwise required by law. 

We store information in the United States. 

If you live outside of the United States, you understand and agree that we may transfer your information to the United States. This site is subject to U.S. laws, which may not afford the same level of protection as those in your country.  

We may link to other sites or have third party services on our site we don't control. 

If you click on a link to a third party site, you will be taken to Web sites we do not control. This includes our pages on social media sites. This policy does not apply to the privacy practices of these Web sites. Read the privacy policy of other Web sites and insurance carriers carefully. We are not responsible for these third party practices.  

Feel free to contact us if you have any questions.

| If you have any questions about this Policy, please e-mail us at [edgeparkcareteam@edgepark.com](mailto:edgeparkcareteam@edgepark.com).   
---|---  
|    
  | You can also write to us or call at:  | Edgepark Medical Supplies  
1810 Summit Commerce Park  
Twinsburg, OH 44087             
Phone: (330) 963-6996  
Toll-Free: (888) 394-5375  

We may update this Policy. 

From time to time we may change our privacy policies. We will notify you of any material changes to our Policy as required by law. We will also post an updated copy on our Web site. Please check our site periodically for updates. 

**notice of privacy practices**  
---  

* * *
